William Francis Gray Swann Papers 1903-1962 Mss.B.Sw1
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1916-1958; 3.0 Linear feet
  - Franklin Institute, 1934; 41 items (Box 17)
    Bartol lab policy and administration
  - Franklin Institute. Cresson Medal, 1948-1960; 10 items (Box 17)
    Re: Swann's receipt of Cresson Medal
  - Franklin Institute -- Library, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Franklin Institute -- Medal Meeting, 1934; 10 items (Box 17)
  - Franz, Frederick, 1943-1956; 22 items (Box 17)
  - Fraser, Everett, 1936; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Fravel, F. R., 1924; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frazer, John, 1936-1955; 4 folders (Box 17)
    - Folder 1, 1936-1941 (Box 17)
    - Folder 2, 1944 (Box 17)
    - Folder 3, 1945-19486 (Box 17)
    - Folder 4, 1947-1955 (Box 17)
  - Frederiksen, D. M., 1936; 9 items (Box 17)
  - Free, E. E., 1926; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Freeman, Ira M., 1944; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Freeman, J. C., 1945; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Freet, Herbert L., 1937; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Frenkel, J., 1930-1931; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Frenkiel, F. N., 1955-1957; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Fretter, W. B., 1947; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Friedman, Herbert, 1949; 8 items (Box 18)
  - Friel, Francis S., 1951; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Friend, A. G., 1935; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Frost, C., 1943; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Fry, David L., 1956; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Fry, Howard M., 1943; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Fry, James C., 1959; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Fry, William F., 1950; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Fulcher, Gordon S., 1919-1947; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Fulweiler, W. H., 1946; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Funk, N. E., 1951; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Furrow, Clarence Lee, 1951; 6 items (Box 18)
  - Fusfield, Herbert I., 1951-1953; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Gagge, Col. A. P., 1956; 4 items (Box 18)
  - Gaims, Horace M., 1948; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gale, Henry G., 1922-1931; 21 items (Box 18)
  - Gammon, Roland, 1958; 8 items (Box 18)
  - Gannon, Robert I., 1944; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gaposchkin, Cecilia Payne, 1959-1960; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Garard, Ira D., 1937; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Garber, Paul Edward, 1947; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Garstick, George A., 1938; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gash-Stull Company, 1938; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gaskell, Grace T., 1939; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gaskill, Harold V., 1938; 6 items (Box 18)
  - Gates, Thomas S., 1937-1938; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gavit, Walter Palmer, 1955; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Geddes, Donald Porter, 1957; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Geiser, Esther, 1955; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gemmill, Raymond R., 1959-1960; 4 items (Box 18)
  - General Chemical Company, 1926; 2 items (Box 18)
  - George Walter F., 1949; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gerard, R. W., 1941; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gerjuoy, Edward, 1951; 3 items (Box 18)
  - Gesensway, Louis, 1953; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gershater, E. M., 1951; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gherzi, E., 1957; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Ghosh, J. C., 1953; 1 item (Box 18)
  - Gibbons, W. M., 1936; items (Box 18)
  - Gibbons-Neff, Morton, 1956; 2 items (Box 18)
  - Gibbs, Becket, 1932-1954; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Folder 1, 1932-1939 (Box 18)
    - Folder 2, 1943-1947 (Box 18)
    - Folder 3, 1948-1954 (Box 18)
  - Gibbs, R. C., 1927-1956; 7 items (Box 18)
  - Gibbs, Willard -- Memorial, 1927-1933; 5 folders (Box 18)
    - Folder 1, 1927-1928 (Box 18)
    - Folder 2, 1929 (Box 18)
    - Folder 3, 1930-1931 (Box 18)
    - Folder 4, 1932 (Box 18)
    - Folder 5, 1933 (Box 18)
  - Gibson, Norman R., 1945-1960; 19 items (Box 18)
  - Gilbert, William O., 1941-1942; 5 items (Box 18)
  - Gilfillan, E. S., Commander, 1947; 4 items (Box 18)
    Operation Crossroads
  - Gill, P. S., 1948-1954; 38 items (Box 19)
  - Gingrich, Newell S., 1946; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Ginn and Company, 1923-1924; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Giraut-Erler, Prof., 1940-1941; 8 items (Box 19)
  - Githens, Sherwood, Jr., 1956; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Glazer, W. H., 1953-1954; 8 items (Box 19)
  - Glenn, Nancy S., 1948-1962; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Folder 1, 1948-1953 (Box 19)
    - Folder 2, 1954-1957 (Box 19)
    - Folder 3, 1958-1962 (Box 19)
  - Glynn, Raymond, 1936; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goddard, George W., 1942; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Godfrey, 1930; 4 items (Box 19)
  - Goetz, Philip W., 1958; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Goff, John A., 1944; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goheen, Harry, 1952; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Goldsmith, Alfred, 1945-1961; 16 items (Box 19)
  - Goldstein, Franklin, 1948-1949; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goldwater, Daniel L., 1943-1944; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Golton, Harold, 1953; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Good, Wilfred M., 1957; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Goodchild, Donald, 1946; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goodell, Warren F., 1955; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Goodnick, Joan, 1956; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Goodspeed, Arthur W., 1935; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Goodwin, Sylvia, 1936; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Goodyear-Zeppelin Corporation, 1933; 2 items (Box 19)
    Includes confidential report on stratospheric balloons
  - Gorham, W. A., 1937; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gorman, Frank D., 1934-1936; 4 items (Box 19)
  - Gorodetzer, Joseph, 1936; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1951-1961; 31 items (Box 19)
  - Goyer, Marie, 1931-1932; 6 items (Box 19)
  - Grant, Hugh Duncan, 1936-1948; 12 items (Box 19)
  - Grasselli Chemical Company, 1924; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1925-1927; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gravity Research Foundation, 1960-1961; 5 items (Box 19)
  - Gray, Arthur W., 1925; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gray, Gertrude, 1938; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gray, Richard M., 1961; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Great Chebeague Gold Club (Maine), 1937-1938; 12 items (Box 19)
  - Grebe, John J., 1954-1957; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Greco, Mrs., 1961; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Green, Chester, 1960-1961; 9 items (Box 19)
  - Green, David Bonnell, 1960; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Green, John R., 1957; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Greenall, Charles H., 1946-1955; 15 items (Box 19)
  - Greenewalt, Crawford H., 1955; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Greenewalt, Mary Hallock, 1947; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Greenfield, E. W., 1949; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Greenlee, George A., 1957; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Gregory, H. F., Gen., 1958; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Gregory, Helen C., 1922; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gregory, Stewart E., 1950; 4 items (Box 19)
  - Grieve, Averil MacKenzie, 1946; 3 items (Box 19)
  - Griffin, James J., 1958; 6 items (Box 19)
  - Griffin, Patrick J., 1936; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Griffith, Ivor, 1950; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Grigorieff, W. W., 1954; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Grolle, Johan, 1930-1937; 15 items (Box 19)
  - Gronowetter, Freda, 1960; 1 item (Box 19)
  - Gross, Berhard, 1946-1954; 21 items (Box 19)
  - Grossman, Louis I., 1950-1951; 4 items (Box 19)
  - Grosvenor, Melville, 1946; 8 items (Box 19)
  - Grout, F. F., 1921; 2 items (Box 19)
  - Groves, Albert H., 1934-1954; 28 items (Box 19)
  - Gruber, Frederick C., 1937-1960; 37 items (Box 20)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C., 1936; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Grummann, H. R., 1957; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Gruner, P., 1927; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Gruner, Wayne, 1954; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Guffey, Joseph, 1945; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Guggenheimer, Samuel H., 1936; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Gupta, N. Das, 1946-1947; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Gupta, P. C., 1950; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Gupta, U. C., 1949; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Gurarye, Jacob, 1936; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Haanes, Vivian I., 1960; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haas, E. G., 1945; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haber, Fred, 1955-1961; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hafsted, L. R., 1950; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hager, Cyril F., 1960; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hake, J. W., 1930-1931; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hale, George E., 1935; 5 items (Box 20)
  - Hale, O. J., 1942; 5 items (Box 20)
  - Halfpenny, S. E., 1938; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hall, Clarence A., 1934-1942; 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Folder 1, 1934-1936 (Box 20)
    - Folder 2, 1937 (Box 20)
    - Folder 3, 1938 (Box 20)
    - Folder 4, 1939-1942 (Box 20)
  - Hall, Edwin H., 1931; 8 items (Box 20)
  - Hall, John S., 1940; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hall, Samuel S., Jr., 1927; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hall, Thomas S., 1950; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Halliday, William B., 1934; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hallock, Joseph, 1944; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hallstein, Raymond F., 1940; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Ham, L. B., 1949; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, Edward P., 1932-1952; 22 items (Box 20)
    John Wiley & Sons
  - Hamilton, Howard S., 1926; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, W. H., 1927; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hamilton Watch Company, 1934-1935; 11 items (Box 20)
  - Hamlin, Chauncy J., 1938; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hancock, Allan, 1945; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Hancock, J. Julian, 1948; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haney, John L., 1939; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hans, H. S., 1956-1959; 5 items (Box 20)
  - Hanson, Howard, 1955; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hanstein, Kathleen Hambly, 1941; 4 items (Box 20)
    American Friends Service Committee; Felix Ehrenhaft
  - Harbold, Mary L., 1955; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Harding, E. P., 1922; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hardtwig, Erwin, 1949; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Harker, A. F. Herrenden, 1946; 9 items (Box 20)
  - Harmer, 1911; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P., 1941-1958; 18tems (Box 20)
  - Harper, C. H., 1936; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harper, Sydney, 1928, 1933; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harrington, E. L., 1936; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harrington, Joseph D., 1944; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harris, Edward G., 1959; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Harris, Ernest E., 1955-1960; 17 items (Box 20)
  - Harris, Henry S., 1949; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Harris, Roger, 1959; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Harrison, J. Kearsley M., 1919-1940; 5 items (Box 20)
    Mine mechanism
  - Harrison, R. G., 1953; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hart, Harry C., 1935-1945; 7 items (Box 20)
  - Hart, Thomas C., 1943-1945; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hartford, Ernest, 1955-1956; 6 items (Box 20)
  - Harvard University, 1929-1939; 20 items (Box 20)
  - Harvard University Tercentenary Conference, 1936; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Harvie, Looie E., 1911; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hatcher, Anna G., 1937-1938; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hatfield, H. Stafford, 1936; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Haupt, Max, 1954; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hausmann, Erich, 1938; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Havens, Paul Swain, 1948; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hawley, Everett M., 1940-1941; 2 items (Box 20)
  - Hayakawa, Satio, 1961; 3 items (Box 20)
  - Hayes, Marian, 1939; 4 items (Box 20)
  - Hayward, n.d.; 1 item (Box 20)
  - Hayward, C. N., 1937-1939; 7 items (Box 21)
  - Hayward, Nathan, 1934-1935; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hazard, Rowland, 1943; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Head, Joseph, 1961; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Heath, Spencer, 1956; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Heck, Lewis O., 1945; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heck, N. H., 1937; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heckert, Robert, 1952; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heckler, H. Frederick, 1953; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heidmann, J., 1954-1958; 6items (Box 21)
  - Heinz, Maurice L., 1947; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Helander, Linn, 1939-1940; 28 items (Box 21)
  - Heller, Edward, 1955-1961; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hellmer, Joseph, 1945; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hemmendinger, Arthur, 1957; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Henderson, Evelyn Colpitts, 1928-1929; 9 items (Box 21)
  - Henderson, Joseph L., 1940; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hendl, Walter, 1943; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hendricks, Grace, 1937-1941; 14 items (Box 21)
  - Hennig, Frank, 1945; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Henny, George C., 1943; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Henry, E. G., 1958; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Henry, Joel C., 1924; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hereford, Frank L., 1952-1959; 13 items (Box 21)
  - Hering, Carl, 1923-1925; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Hermann, Edward W., 1956; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hermann, Emil, 1937; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Herr, Donald L., 1938-1939; 16 items (Box 21)
    ESP
  - Herrick, Gerard P., 1937-1938; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Herrmann, Otto, 1937; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Herskowitz, Morton, 1960; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hertlein, Lotta, 1954; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Herzfeld, S. H., 1960; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hess, Victor F., 1921-1952; 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Folder 1, 1921-1939 (Box 21)
    - Folder 2, 1940 (Box 21)
    - Folder 3, 1941 (Box 21)
    - Folder 4, 1942 (Box 21)
    - Folder 5, 1943-1947 (Box 21)
    - Folder 6, 1950-1952 (Box 21)
  - Hessler, V. P., 1952; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Heuertz, Charles W., 1944; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hewitt, Oscar E., 1951; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hewlett, C. W., 1914, 1946; 3 items (Box 21)
  - Heyer, Anna Harriet, 1947; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Heyl, Paul R., 1935-1948; 11 items (Box 21)
  - Hibben, James M., 1927; 5 items (Box 21)
  - Hibbert, H. Wesley, 1944; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hicks, Victor, 1930; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hicks, W. M., 1917-1930; 10 items (Box 21)
  - Higgins, George M., 1936; 2 items (Box 21)
  - High, Jurjon S., 1947; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hilger, Maria, 1937; 7 items (Box 21)
  - Hill, E., 1932; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hill, J. M., 1943; 7 items (Box 21)
  - Hill, M. J. M., 1906; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hill, W. E. & Sons, 1937; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hille, Einar, 1927; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hindemith, Paul, 1945; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hipple, Arthur R. von, 1951-1955; 4 items (Box 21)
  - Hirsch, Carl E., 1957; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hitchcock, William J., 1956; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hoadley, George A., 1935; 1 item (Box 21)
  - Hoadley, George B., 1956; 2 items (Box 21)
  - Hobaugh, Lester W., 1945-1946; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hocking, Ernest, 1958; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hodes, Robert, 1945; 5 items (Box 22)
  - Hodges, Clarence A., 1959; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hoffman, Banesh, 1948; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hoffmann, G., 1934; 13 items (Box 22)
    Re: Millikan on stosse; W. Messerschmidt
  - Hoffmann, Mima Wagner, 1938; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hoffsommer, Alfred, 1947-1952; 7 items (Box 22)
  - Hogg, W. E., 1907; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hohler, G. Robert, 1961; 12 items (Box 22)
  - Holbrook, Richard T., 1931; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holden, A., 1909; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holden, Thomas, 1944; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hollander, Joseph Lee, 1956-1961; 11 items (Box 22)
  - Hollingsworth, Albert D., 1954-1961; 31 items (Box 22)
  - Hollingsworth, L. M., 1946; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Holloway, John T., 1950-1952; 15 items (Box 22)
  - Holmes, M. C., 1936; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Holmes, W. H., 1948-1949; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Holmquist, Fred M., 1961; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Holroyd, Howard B., 1935; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1959-1960; 5 items (Box 22)
  - Holzer, Robert E., 1943-1954; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hook, James W., 1928; 10 items (Box 22)
  - Hooven, C. Warren, 1944; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hopkins, Arthur H., 1959; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hopwood, F. Lloyd, 1943; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hornaday, James H., 1947; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Horner, Martha G., 1941-1957; 11 items (Box 22)
  - Hornyak, William F., 1951; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Horton, Gerald B., 1952; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Horvath, A. G., 1927; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Hotchkiss, W. E., 1936; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Houghton, Donald B., 1953; 5 items (Box 22)
    Includes copies of SIAM Newsletter
  - Houghland, Willard, 1944-1945; 6 items (Box 22)
  - Houston, W. V., 1961; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Howard, Bruce W., 1955-1956; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Howard, Edgar, Jr., 1953; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Howell, Lewis James, 1945-1948; 9 items (Box 22)
  - Howey, Joseph H., 1945; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Howson and Howson, 1929; 17 items (Box 22)
  - Hoyer, Louis P., 1951; 4 items (Box 22)
  - Hubbard, J. C., 1928-1942; 9 items (Box 22)
  - Hubbard, L. Ron, 1960; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Huckabee Weyman C., 1956-1958; 36 items (Box 22)
    Re: science and relgion. Includes essay by Swann, "Statement of a Creed to Enable Those Concerned to Crystallize Their Own Thoughts as to Their Belief in Various Matters Ordinarily Regarded as in the Occult Realm"
  - Hudson, Ralph G., 1945; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Hudspeth, Emmett L., 1939-1950; 5 folders (Box 22)
    - Folder 1, 1939-1941 (Box 22)
    - Folder 2, 1942 (Box 22)
    - Folder 3, 1943-1944 (Box 22)
    - Folder 4, 1945-1948 (Box 22)
    - Folder 5, 1949-1950 (Box 22)
  - Huey, R. M., 1960; 2 items (Box 22)
  - Huggins, W. H., 1960; 1 item (Box 22)
  - Hughan, Ruth, 1944; 3 items (Box 22)
  - Hughes, A. L., 1930-1951; 20 items (Box 22)
  - Hughes, D. J., 1954-1955; 8 items (Box 23)
  - Hughes, Harold K., 1938; 7 items (Box 23)
  - Hughes, Hunter, 1953; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Hulburt, E. O., 1954; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Hull, Albert W., 1946; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Hull, Gordon F., 1932-1954; 28 items (Box 23)
  - Hullihen, Walter, 1937-1943; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Hultberg, Edward, Jr., Lt., 1942; 52 items (Box 23)
    Geiger tubes
  - Humphreys, W. J., 1927-1935; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Hunsaker, J. C., 1919; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Hunt, Mrs. E. T., 1945; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Hunt, Everett, 1943-1953; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Hunt, J. Beeson, 1951; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Huntoon, R. D., 1960; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hurlburt, E. O., 1956; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hurley, Patrick J., 1933; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hurst, William M., 1959; 3 items (Box 23)
    Includes photo of Hurst
  - Hu, Shih, 1945; 7 items (Box 23)
    Re: Fung Hon-Ko
  - Hutchinson, A., 1931; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Hutcheson, J. A., 1958; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchins, L. W., 1934; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1931; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchinson, G. L., 1955; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchinson, H. B., 1947; 15 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchison, Clyde A., 1955; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Hutchison, F. C., 1952; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchison, Ralph C., 1945-1946; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Hutchisson, Elmer, 1945-1961; 5 items (Box 23)
  - Huyett, W. I., 1960; 4 items (Box 23)
  - Hyde, Arthur D., 1947; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Ice, Herschel C., 1939-1941; 4 items (Box 23)
  - Ide, G. M., 1948; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Imes, Elmer S., 1930; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Imperial College of Science and Technology, 1956-1958; 8 items (Box 23)
  - India Supply Mission, 1950; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Ingersoll, A. W., 1936; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Ingram, H. E., 1950-1951; 8 items (Box 23)
  - International Resistance Company, 1935; 3 items (Box 23)
  - International Who's Who, 1937; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Ions, Clarendon, 1924; 1 item (Box 23)
  - Irion, Clarence E., 1936; 3 items (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Dunham, 1925; 2 items (Box 23)
  - Jackson, Irwin, E., Jr., 1937-1950; 13 items (Box 23)
  - Jackson, William F., Jr., 1925-1961; 21 folders (Box 23)
    - Folder 1, 1925-1927 (Box 23)
      Bartol Institute
    - Folder 2, 1930 (Box 23)
    - Folder 3, 1931 (Box 23)
    - Folder 4, 1932 (Box 23)
    - Folder 5, 1933-1934 (Box 23)
    - Folder 6, 1935-1936 (Box 23)
    - Folder 7, 1937-1942 (Box 23)
    - Folder 8, 1943 (Box 23)
    - Folder 9, 1944 (Box 23)
    - Folder 10, 1945 (Box 23)
    - Folder 11, 1946 (Box 24)
    - Folder 12, 1947 (Box 24)
    - Folder 13, 1948 Jan.-June (Box 24)
    - Folder 14, 1948 July-Dec. (Box 24)
    - Folder 15, 1949 Jan.-June (Box 24)
    - Folder 16, 1949 July-Dec. (Box 24)
    - Folder 17, 1950 Jan.-June (Box 24)
    - Folder 18, 1950 July-Dec. (Box 24)
    - Folder 19, 1951 (Box 24)
    - Folder 20, 1952-1953 (Box 24)
    - Folder 21, 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Jacobs, Charles, 1942; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Jacobs, Sidney J., 1946; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Jacobsohn, Samuel, 1928; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Jaffe, Bernard, 1933; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Jaffe, Isaac, 1953; 5 items (Box 24)
  - Jaffey, Arthur H., 1959; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Jain, P. C., 1957; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Jakeman, D., 1953; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Jambor, Agi, 1948-1959; 10 items (Box 24)
  - James, Benjamin F., 1949; 1 item (Box 24)
  - James, Robert F., 1930; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Janney, J. Elliott, 1951; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Jánossy, Lajos, 1948-1949; 5 items (Box 24)
  - Japan. Consulate General. New York (N.Y.), 1961; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Jaquette, William A., 1936-1940; 6 items (Box 24)
  - Jastrow, Joseph, 1934-1936; 20 items (Box 24)
  - Jauch, J. M., 1949; 10 items (Box 24)
  - Jehle, Herbert, 1945-1961; 20 items (Box 24)
    Pacifism. Includes photo
  - Jen, C. K., 1961; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Jenkins, Horace C., 1954; 1 item (Box 24)
  - Jenkins, Howard M., 1949-1950; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Jesse, William P., 1938; 4 items (Box 24)
  - Jevons, W., 1946-1947; 6 items (Box 24)
  - Jewett, Frank B., 1944-1945; 19 items (Box 24)
    Frank Bludworth; American Philosophical Society statement on scientific service and the war
  - Jilbert, Marvin C., 1940; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Joffé, Mark, 1946-1947; 17 items (Box 24)
  - John P. Donohue & Sons, 1943; 11 items (Box 24)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1926-1929; 16 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, A. Francis, 1935; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, E. R. Fenimore, 1952; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Ellis A., 1950-1952; 8 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Emory R., 1944; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, Irmis, 1946; 2 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, J. B., 1954-1957; 7 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, John, 1941; 3 items (Box 24)
  - Johnson, M. A., 1937; 3 items (Box 25)
  - Johnson, R. P., 1948; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Regina B., 1939-1940; 4 items (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Robert L., 1953-1954; 3 items (Box 25)
    Temple University
  - Johnson, Thomas H., 1929-1959; 18 folders (Box 25)
    Cosmic ray studies; South American and Mexican expeditions
    - Folder 1, 1929 (Box 25)
    - Folder 2, 1930 (Box 25)
    - Folder 3, 1931 Jan.-June (Box 25)
    - Folder 4, 1931 July-Dec. (Box 25)
    - Folder 5, 1932 Jan.-June (Box 25)
    - Folder 6, 1932 July-Sep. (Box 25)
    - Folder 7, 1932 Oct.-Dec. (Box 25)
    - Folder 8, 1933 Jan.-Feb. (Box 25)
    - Folder 9, 1933 Mar. (Box 25)
    - Folder 10, 1933 Apr.-May (Box 25)
    - Folder 11, 1933 June (Box 25)
    - Folder 12, 1933 July-Dec. (Box 25)
    - Folder 13, 1934 (Box 25)
    - Folder 14, 1935-1937 (Box 25)
    - Folder 15, 1938-1940 (Box 25)
    - Folder 16, 1941-1945 (Box 25)
    - Folder 17, 1946 (Box 25)
    - Folder 18, 1947-1959 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Vincent, 1921; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Johnson, Walker, 1960-1961; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Johnston, J. B., 1921-1928; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Johnston, John, 1926; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Johnston, John P.M., 1948; 15 items (Box 26)
  - Johnston, Richard W., 1952; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Joiner, T. D., 1952; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Jolly, S. E., 1950; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Jones, Arthur Gordon, 1958-1959; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Frederick S., 1924; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Gertrude F., 1958; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Ivor R., 1952-1953; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Malcolm S., 1952-1953; 9 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Palmer, 1942; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Robert T., 1960; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Roderick B., 1948-1952; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Jones, Thomas E., 1940; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Jordan, Clarence L., 1954; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Journal of the Franklin Institute. Correspondence, 1928-1935 (Box 26)
  - Judd, David L., 1959; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Judson, Harry Pratt, 1922; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Jurgens, Marion A., 1948; 8 items (Box 26)
  - Justi, Henry M., 1940-1955; 10tems (Box 26)
  - Kable, Brothers Company, 1951; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1934-1951; 43 items (Box 26)
  - Kahn, Gordon S., 1938-1951; 12items (Box 26)
  - Kalcik, Vaclav V., 1928; 6 items (Box 26)
    Theory of gravitation from resident of anarchist Mohegan Colony
  - Kaminsky, Abram, 1938; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Kamp, Peter Van de, 1938-1942; 7 items (Box 26)
  - Kane, Albert M., 1960-1961; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Kanenstine, F. M., 1924; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kanner, Oscar, 1952-1953; 24 items (Box 26)
    Musical cybernetics
  - Kapelski, Marion Stanley, 1951-1953; 4 items (Box 26)
    See; also: Necho, Louis
  - Karapetoff, Vladimir, 1932-1945; 20 items (Box 26)
  - Karch, Frederic L., 1961; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Katcher, David A., 1950-1951; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Kaufman, Scrima, 1934; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Kaysing, C. W., 1958; 5 items (Box 26)
  - Keane, Robert L., 1954-1959; 9 items (Box 26)
  - Keenan, Joseph H., 1929; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Keenan, V. J., 1954-1955; 6 items (Box 26)
  - Keevil, N. B., 1944; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Keim, Lucia, 1947; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Keller, W. S., 1952; 4 items (Box 26)
  - Kellogg, Paul J., 1957; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Kellogg, Vernon, 1924; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kelly, E. L., 1925; 1 item (Box 26)